[
    {
        "front": "いく",
        "back": "行く \nTo go",
        "chapter": "N5 K9"
    },
    {
        "front": "くる",
        "back": "来る \nTo come",
        "chapter": "N5 K9"
    },
    {
        "front": "らいねん",
        "back": "来年 \nNext year",
        "chapter": "N5 K9"
    },
    {
        "front": "らいしゅう",
        "back": "来週 \nNext week",
        "chapter": "N5 K9"
    },
    {
        "front": "たべる",
        "back": "食べる \nTo eat",
        "chapter": "N5 K9"
    },
    {
        "front": "みる",
        "back": "見る \nTo see, to look at",
        "chapter": "N5 K9"
    },
    {
        "front": "みせる",
        "back": "見せる \nTo show",
        "chapter": "N5 K9"
    },
    {
        "front": "はいる",
        "back": "入る \nTo enter",
        "chapter": "N5 K9"
    },
    {
        "front": "いれる",
        "back": "入れる \nTo put in",
        "chapter": "N5 K9"
    },
    {
        "front": "いりぐち",
        "back": "入口 \nEntrance",
        "chapter": "N5 K9"
    },
    {
        "front": "にゆうがくする",
        "back": "入学する \nTo enter a school",
        "chapter": "N5 K9"
    },
    {
        "front": "でる",
        "back": "出る \nTo go/ come out",
        "chapter": "N5 K9"
    },
    {
        "front": "だす",
        "back": "出す \nTo take out",
        "chapter": "N5 K9"
    },
    {
        "front": "でぐち",
        "back": "出口 \nExit",
        "chapter": "N5 K9"
    },
    {
        "front": "たつ",
        "back": "立つ \nTo stand",
        "chapter": "N5 K9"
    },
    {
        "front": "かく",
        "back": "書く \nTo write",
        "chapter": "N5 K9"
    },
    {
        "front": "いう",
        "back": "言う \nTo say",
        "chapter": "N5 K9"
    },
    {
        "front": "のむ",
        "back": "飲む \nTo drink",
        "chapter": "N5 K9"
    }
]